https://www.midmetal.com.sg/privacy

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy is for this website www.midmetal.com.sg, www.midmetal.com.au and served by Midland Metals Overseas Pte Ltd and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is
concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users,
the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website
processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be
detailed within this policy.
This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user
privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy
of its users
throughout their visiting experience. This website
complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.Use of Cookies
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while
visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie
control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to
allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This
complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain
explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such
as cookies on a user's computer / device.
Cookies are small files saved to the user's computers hard drive
that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and
usage of
the website. This allows the website, through its server to
provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.
Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of
cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should
take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to
block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors.
This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to
better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google
Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will
save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor
your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or
collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here
for further information [ http://www.google.com/privacy.html ].
Other cookies may be stored to your computers hard drive by external
vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or
adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and
typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal
information is stored, saved or collected.
Contact & Communication
Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own
discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own
risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely
until a time it is no longer required or has no use. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe
and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such
form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.
This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide
you with further information about the products / services they offer
or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have
submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any
email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made
clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any
form to email process. Or whereby you the consumer have previously
purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product
or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an
entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing
material.
Your details are not passed on to any third parties.
Email Newsletter
This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform
subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. Users
can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do
so but do so at their own discretion. Some subscriptions may be
manually processed through prior written agreement with the user.
Email marketing campaigns published by this website or its owners
may contain tracking facilities within the actual email. Subscriber
activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and
evaluation. Such tracked activity may include; the opening of emails,
forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content,
times, dates and frequency of activity [this is by no far a
comprehensive list].
This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply
the user with more relevant content based around their activity.
Subscribers are given the opportunity to
un-subscribe at any time through an automated system. This process is
detailed at the footer of each email campaign. If an automated
un-subscription system is unavailable clear instructions on how to
un-subscribe will by detailed instead.
